Guide to the Stages Theater records, 1978-2017 MS 740
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Development (boxes 26-30 - restricted), 1981-2004
  - Lillian Kaiser Lewis Foundation, 1984-1999 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Kayser Foundation, 1996-2004 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Ben E. Keith Foundation, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Kempner Fund, 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - The Kennedy Center, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Knox Charitable Foundation, 1986-1993 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Knox Foundation, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1984-1993 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Linda & Ken Lay Family, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Linbeck Foundation, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Margaret Love Foundation, 1995-2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Lowe Foundation, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Mabee Foundation, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Mac-Donald Peterson Foundation, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Main Stage License Agreement, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Marketing, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Martel Foundation, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - McCrea Foundation, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - McGovern Fund, 1988-1999 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - McNair Foundation, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Meadows Foundation, 1983-1996 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Mellon Foundation, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Met Life Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Moody Foundation, 1982-1993 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Mosbacher Foundation, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Nalco Foundation, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - NEA, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - NEA, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NEA - Artist Residency, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Creation & Presentation, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - NEA - Education & Access, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - NEA - Evaluation, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - NEA Grant, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - NEA - Planning & Stabilization, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - NEA/TCG Residency Program, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Nightingale Code Foundation, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Opening of Pinter Plays, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing donations, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Owsley Foundation, 1984-2001 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Pembroke Foundation, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Polaroid Corporation, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - The Powell Foundation, 1995-2003 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Francesca R. Primus Foundation, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Princess Grace Foundation USA, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Proposal Progress Reports, 1990-1995 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - PSH Foundation, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Redman Foundation, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Sid Richardson Foundation, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Rienzi Foundation, 1978-1990 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - George A. Robinson, IV Foundation, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1990-2004 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Rockwell Fund, 1982-1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - The Roff Foundation, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Rowley Foundation, 1996-2005 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Judith and Henry Sauer Charitable Foundation, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Schissler Charitable Foundation, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - School Residency Program, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Scriptwriters, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Scurlock Foundation, 1987-1993 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Walter P. Sharp Memorial Foundation, 1989-1994 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Shubert Foundation, 1987-2000 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Vivian L. Smith, 1990-2004 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Sterling-Turner Foundation, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Sterling-Turner Foundation Fund, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Strake Foundation, 1988-2001 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Strategic Plan, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Swalm Foundation, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - TCG Forms and Information, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - TCG National Conference, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Tellepsen Foundation, 1987-1989 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 3M Foundation, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Texas Institute for Arts in Education, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Theta Charity Antiques Show, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Union Pacific Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Vaughn Foundation, 1997-2004 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - The Wallpaper Project, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Webber Foundation, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Weems Foundation, 1991-1995 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - West Foundation, 1988-1998 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Williams Company, 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Wise Family Foundation, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Work Study Program, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Wortham Foundation, 1982-1992 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Wortham Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Wortham Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Wortham Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Wray Charitable Trust, 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Young Audiences Partnership, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Young Audiences Sales Agreement, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Series IV: Events (boxes 31-32), 1996-2016
  - Stages Gala, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Searching for Eden Gala, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Searching for Eden Gala, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Stardust Gala, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Gala Budgets, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 30th Anniversary Gala, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Gala Hullaba-Luau, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Season Opener Gala The Mame Event, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Gala Be Marvelous!, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Gala: The Costume Ball, 2012 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Gala: 1978 Glitter and Glam, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Gala Xanadu, 2014 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Gala: Talk of the Town, 2016 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Express Theater: Wonka, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Actor's Theater of Houston, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Paella on the Patio Benefit, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Stagefest, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Parties/Benefits, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Donor Events, 2015-2016 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Southwest Festival of New Plays, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Southwest Festival of New Plays, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Southwest Festival of New Plays, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Texas Playwrights' Festival, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Texas Playwrights' Festival, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Tiffany in Fashion, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Tiffany in Fashion Guests, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Unbeatable: A New Musical (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Winefest, 1990-1999 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Women's Repertory Project, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Women's Repertory Project, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Building Rentals (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Celebrity Councils, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Cocktail Party, 2003-10-08 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Stars, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Stars Invitations, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Gala: Swingin' on a Star, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Gala, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Lanier Gala, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Gala, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Gala Backstages: An Evening Behind the Scenes, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - 20th Anniversary Gala "A Memoir of the American Musical Theater", 1998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Full Gallop Gala, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Roasting Lynn Ashby Benefit, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Roasting Lynn Ashby Gala, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Gala: Favors, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Gala: Houston Country Club, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Gala: Invitation Material, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Roasting Lynn Ashby Gala: Program Information, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Gala "Roasters", 2000 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Gala: Underwriters, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Gala: "Uncommon Theater", 2000 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Dedication of the John Yeager Theater, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Gala: "Stages...in the Spotlight", 2001 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Gala: A Celebration of American Fashion, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - And All that Jazz, 2003-05-08 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - A Fare Extraordinaire Event, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - 25th Anniversary Gala: The Silver Ball, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - The Silver Ball: Tickets, 2004-03-27 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Gala: An Evening of Fractured Fairy Tales, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Series V: Photography (boxes 33-35), 1980-2005
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical
    - Alicia in Wonder Tierra (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bent (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Berlin, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - BK, 1987-10 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Blood Knot, 1987-10 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Blood Wedding (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Blues in the Night (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Blues in the Night (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Blue Window, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Bowling (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Bowling Microfilm (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Boy Meets Girl (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Carol Neacey (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - CC Press Shots (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Charlotte's Web (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Chili Queen (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Colored Museum, 1988-2001 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Colored Museum (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Communicating Doors (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Company Pictures (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Cyrano (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Danny and the Deep Blue Sea (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Daughters of Heaven (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - The Day they Shot Lennon, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Dirty Blonde (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Doonesbury (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Drawer Boy (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Driving Miss Daisy Contact Sheet (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Early Stages, Elena/Sandra (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Early Stages: Kid's Day (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Elizabeth Rex (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - The Firebird (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Front of Theater (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Gift of the Magi (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Gin Game, 1982-04 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Glass Menagerie, 1987-04 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Hair (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Heidi (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Highest / Lulu (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - House That I Call Love, The (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - John and Jeun Yenger Theater (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Importance of Being Earnest, The (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Isn't it Romantic? (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Jane Eyre / Town Montgomery (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Jim Caldwell (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Just So Stories (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - K2, 1985-01 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - La Bella Soeurs (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - La Mancha (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Laramie Project, The (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Laughing Wild (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Leader, 1962-12 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Leana A-Z (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Lessons from Aloes (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Little Egypt (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Little Prince, The (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Little Prince, The (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Little Witch / Pavilion Publicity Shots (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Lulu (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Mad / Memo Pres Photo (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Mandy Kate Brown, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Marry Me a Little, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Marsha Norman, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Merrily, 1987-10 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Mother Goose (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Mother Goose (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Nite-club (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Nunsense (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Paris Libere (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Pitchfork Disney, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Polk (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Pushed1 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Refuge (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Revenge of the Space Pandas (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Romance / Romance and Toys (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Rumpelstilskin (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Salonika (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Seduced (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Seduced (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Sigh Unseen (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Sister Mary, etc. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Sister Mageta, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Sunday Gold (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Syncopation (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Talley and Son, Struttin' and Frettin', Rupert's Birthday (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Tartuffe (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Ted Swindley Portrait (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Texas Playwright's Festival, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - This One Only (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - The Three Treasures of Buccaneer Island (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Time, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Tornado, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Toys and Jacob Mafley (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Toys (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Traveler in the Dark (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Treasure Island (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Velveteen Rabbit, The (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Windmills TDF (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Wings Media Shots (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Winnie the Pooh (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Young Actors Conservatory, Summer, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Subseries B: Date only or Unidentified
    - Unidentified Photographs, 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 1986-2006 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 1991-03-13 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Gala?), 2001 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2001-05-03 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2001-10-24 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2001-11-09 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2002-2006 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Gala?), 2005 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Building?), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Contact Sheets?), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Stage's Manager Promotion?), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Performances?), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Program Headquarters?), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Unidentified Photographs, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1-19)
- Series VI: Audio / Visual recordings (boxes 36-39), 1985-2009
  - Subseries A: 1985-1999
    - Stages, 1985 (id # STAG-0045) Audio, Cassette
    - Archer and The Princess, 1987 (id # STAG-0109) Video, VHS
    - Planes, Trains and Automobiles: The Original Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1987 (id # STAG-0142) Video, VHS
    - Shakin the Mess..., 1989 (id # STAG-0162) Audio, Cassette
    - Mozart Concertos: Oboe, Horn, Clarinet, Flute and Harp, 1990 (id # STAG-0113) Audio, Cassette
    - Talking Pix, 1991 (id # STAG-0166) Audio, Cassette
    - Closer than Ever, 1991 (id # STAG-0167) Audio, Cassette
    - Live at Five KTRK-TV Houston, 1992 (id # STAG-0143) Video, VHS
    - Winnie-the-Pooh + Piglet Good Morning Houston, 1992 (id # STAG-0144) Video, VHS
    - City Council Meeting / Channel Two News at Noon, 1992 (id # STAG-0154) Video, VHS
    - Stages Theater Controversy, 1992 (id # STAG-0155) Audio, Cassette
    - PM Drive KTRH-AM Houston, 1992 (id # STAG-0157) Audio, Cassette
    - City of Houston Buys Star Engraving Building, 1992 (id # STAG-0159) Audio, Cassette
    - Perfect Party, 1992 (id # STAG-0169) Audio, Cassette
    - "Stages Repertory Theater" KTRH-AM Houston, 1992 (id # STAG-0170) Audio, Cassette
    - Channel Two News Weekend KPRC-TV (NBC) Houston 6:00-6:30, 1992 (id # STAG-0208) Video, VHS
    - The Princess and The Stableboy, 1993 (id # STAG-0145) Video, VHS
    - Spirit Drummers Circle, 1993 (id # STAG-0122) Audio, Cassette
    - Ch. 8 Jack and Jill, 1997 (id # STAG-0147) Video, VHS
    - Pinocchio Commedia, 1997 (id # STAG-0095) Video, VHS
    - Laima Gaizutis, "Misty Night" / "Touched" / "Currents of Love", 1997 (id # STAG-0124) Audio, Cassette
    - Funny Girl B Roll 8 Clips, 1998 (id # STAG-0025) Video, Betacam SP
    - Children of Abraham, 1999 (id # STAG-0062) Video, VHS
    - Valley Song, 1999 (id # STAG-0171) Audio, Cassette
    - Kindertransport, 1999 (id # STAG-0173) Audio, Cassette
    - The Magical Birthday Pinata, 1999 (id # STAG-0108) Audio, Cassette
    - The Dying Gaul, 1999 (id # STAG-0190) Video, VHS
    - Full Gallop Promo, 1999 (id # STAG-0210) Video, VHS
    - Full Gallop Promo, 1999 (id # STAG-0130) Video, VHS
  - Subseries B: 2000-2003
    - KUHF God's Man (?), 2000 (id # STAG-0174) Audio, Cassette
    - Academics 2000 Jr. Players II field trip, 2000 (id # STAG-0105) Video, VHS
    - Academics 2000 "Jr. Players" Field Trip, 2000 (id # STAG-0106) Video, VHS
    - Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet Adapted by Joe Calaraco, 2000 (id # STAG-0189) Video, VHS
    - Shows B-Roll Compilation Selects, 2001 (id # STAG-0018) Video, Betacam SP
    - Runt of the Litter Fox 26, 2001 (id # STAG-0149) Video, VHS
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 2001 (id # STAG-0103) Video, VHS
    - Randi Driscoll performs "What Matters" live at Mercyhurst College, 2001 (id # STAG-0096) Video, VHS
    - Fox News Elizabeth Rex (9pm), 2001 (id # STAG-0097) Video, VHS
    - Shell Business Broadcast, 2001 (id # STAG-0185) Video, VHS
    - Interview at Fox 26 with Fran Fawcett, 2001 (id # STAG-0191) Video, VHS
    - B-Roll Compilation No Titles, 2001 (id # STAG-0194) Video, VHS
    - B-Roll Compilation with Titles, 2001 (id # STAG-0110) Video, VHS
    - Shows B-Roll Compilation w/ titles, 2001 (id # STAG-0204) Video, VHS
    - FOX 12:00 Pavillion, 2001 (id # STAG-0218) Video, VHS
      Scope and Contents
      Not digitized.
    - Stages Production B-Roll - "The Toys Take Over Christmas" "Dirty Blonde" "Blood Wedding", 2002 (id # STAG-0001) Video, Betacam SP
    - Stages Theatre 25 Yr. Retrospective Raw Footage Tapes 13-15, 2002 (id # STAG-0015) Video, VHS
    - Laramie Project Promo, 2002 (id # STAG-0017) Video, VHS
    - Blood Wedding B-roll, 2002 (id # STAG-0020) Video, Betacam
    - B-roll, Jacob Marley's Christmas Carol, 2002 (id # STAG-0032) Video, Betacam SP
    - Romance/Laramie KUHF / Wed for Firebird, 2002 (id # STAG-0078) Audio, Cassette
    - "An Oral History" 25th Anniversary Retrospective, 2002 (id # STAG-0038) Video, Betacam SP
    - Blood Wedding, 2002 (id # STAG-0048) Video, Mini DV
    - Stages Laramie Project: B-Roll, 2002 (id # STAG-0049) Video, Mini DV
    - The Laramie Project, 2002 (id # STAG-0178) Video, Betacam SP
    - Laramie Project Promo, 2002 (id # STAG-0068) Video, VHS
    - Craig Wright/Blood Wedding/Jacob Marley's Christmas Carol / Drawer Boy, 2002 (id # STAG-0084) Audio, Cassette
    - B-roll The Toys Take Over Christmas, 2002 (id # STAG-0098) Video, Betacam SP
    - Skeptics, 2002 (id # STAG-0104) Video, VHS
    - B-Roll "The Drawer Boy", 2002 (id # STAG-0193) Video, VHS
    - On Air Spot Member Benefit KUHT, 2002 (id # STAG-0205) Video, VHS
    - The Big Voice: God or Merman, 2002 (id # STAG-0216) Video, VHS
    - Stages Theatre 25-Year Retrospective Raw Footage tapes 9-12, 2002 (id # STAG-0133) Video, VHS
    - Stages/Speaking in Tongues, 2003 (id # STAG-0011) Video, VHS
    - Dirty Blonde KUHF / Syncopation, 2003 (id # STAG-0076) Audio, Cassette
    - B-Roll - Syncopation, 2003 (id # STAG-0035) Video, Betacam SP
    - New Curtains for Macbeth, 2003 (id # STAG-0061) Video, VHS
    - B-Roll: Recent Tragic Events, 2003 (id # STAG-0065) Video, VHS
    - B-Roll Recent Tragic Events, 2003 (id # STAG-0094) Video, Betacam SP
    - KUHF - Bob Stevenson, 2003 (id # STAG-0083) Audio, Cassette
    - Houston PES Member Benefit Sponsor, 2003 (id # STAG-0092) Video, VHS
    - Stages Spring Gala (Don Moser), 2003 (id # STAG-0093) Video, VHS
    - "Bat Boy" (Return to Elena Coates), 2003 (id # STAG-0180) Video, VHS
      Not captured digitally, duplicate of STAG-0186, in this collection.
    - "Bat Boy" (Return to Elena Coates), 2003 (id # STAG-0186) Video, VHS
    - Speaking in Tongues, 2003 (id # STAG-0209) Video, VHS
  - Subseries C: 2004-2005
    - Stages 25th Act V "Community" Rough Edit, 2004 (id # STAG-0010) Video, VHS
    - Queer Voices/Convenience / Front Row/Castro's Beard, 2004 (id # STAG-0079) Audio, Cassette
    - 25th Anniversary Gala Show Videos, 2004 (id # STAG-0041) Video, Betacam SP
    - 40 Miles from Tel Aviv, 2004 (id # STAG-0047) Video, Mini DV
    - "The Toys Take Over Christmas" 2004 Edition, 2004 (id # STAG-0050) Video, Mini DV
    - Continental Airlines Journeys "Best of Texas", 2004 (id # STAG-0058) Video, VHS
    - Toys Take Over Xmas, 2004 (id # STAG-0153) Video, Betacam SP
    - Continental Airlines Journeys "Best of Texas", 2004 (id # STAG-0067) Video, VHS
    - Turner Private Networks Continental Airlines, 2004 (id # STAG-0072) Video, VHS
    - CH8 Member Benefit, 2004 (id # STAG-0179) Video, VHS
      Not captured digitally.
    - B-roll Bat Boy: The Musical, 2004 (id # STAG-0192) Video, VHS
    - Always...Patsy Cline, 2004 (id # STAG-0202) Video, VHS
    - FOX 26 Patsy / About Being, 2004 (id # STAG-0206) Video, VHS
    - Dirty Story B-roll, 2004 (id # STAG-0213) Video, VHS
    - How Anansi the Spider Came to America, Hobby Center, 2005 (id # STAG-0012) Video, Betacam SP
    - "LATE: A Cowboy Song" Selected B-Roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0023) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Baby: A Musical" Selected B-Roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0028) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Baby: A Musical" Selected B-Roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0031) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Silence" Selected B-Roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0033) Video, Betacam SP
    - FM Houston Mineola Twins, 2005 (id # STAG-0080) Audio, Cassette
    - Orange Flower Water 88.7 FM, 2005 (id # STAG-0081) Audio, Cassette
    - The Afterparty #115, 2005 (id # STAG-0037) Video, VHS
      Not captured / tape was blank.
    - Honky Tonk Angels Rehearsal 2005 Act I, 2005 (id # STAG-0051) Video, Mini DV
    - Honky Tonk Angels Rehearsal 2005 Act II, 2005 (id # STAG-0052) Video, Mini DV
    - Young Actors Conservatory 1 of 2, 2005 (id # STAG-0053) Video, Mini DV
    - Young Actors Conservatory 2 of 2, 2005 (id # STAG-0054) Video, Mini DV
    - Channel 8 Member Benefit Reel, 2005 (id # STAG-0057) Video, VHS
    - Peter and the Wolf, 2005 (id # STAG-0158) Audio, Cassette
    - Blank tape, 2005 (id # STAG-0085) Audio, Cassette
      General
      The content of this tape is blank and it has not been preserved digitally.
    - How Anansi the Spider Came to America, Hobby Center, 2005 (id # STAG-0182) Video, Betacam SP
    - How Anansi the Spider Came to America, Hobby Center, 2005 (id # STAG-0100) Video, VHS
    - The Toys Take over Christmas, 2005 (id # STAG-0101) Video, VHS
    - The Toys Take over Christmas, 2005 (id # STAG-0135) Video, VHS
    - LATE: A Cowboy Song by Sarah Ruhl, 2005 (id # STAG-0187) Video, VHS
    - "Honky Tonk Angels" B-roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0112) Video, VHS
    - "The Honky Tonk Angels: by Ted Swindley Selected B-Roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0128) Video, VHS
    - "Silence" Selected B-Roll, 2005 (id # STAG-0215) Video, VHS
  - Subseries D: 2006-2009
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0006) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0014) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Cook" Selected B-roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0022) Video, VHS
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0024) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Great American Trailer Park Musical" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0026) Video, Betacam SP
    - Houston PBS Member Benefit Sponsor, 2006 (id # STAG-0027) Video, VHS
    - "An Infinite Ache" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0029) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0030) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Dead Guy" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0034) Video, Betacam SP
    - "The Great American Trailer Park Musical" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0039) Video, Betacam SP
    - "Five Course Love" Selected B-Roll, 2006 (id # STAG-0040) Video, Betacam SP